The secret life of girls... it's not pretty.
Odd Girl Out is a drama, family, tv movie film directed by Tom McLoughlin.
A mother and her daughter confront the intimidation of teen peer pressure and
the emotionally brutalizing social rituals of high school.
Vanessa, played by Alexa PenaVega.
Barbare, played by Lisa Vidal.
Stacey, played by Leah Pipes.
Nikki, played by Elizabeth Rice.
Tiffany, played by Alicia Morton.
Emily, played by Shari Dyon Perry.
Odd Girl Out is a 2005 drama telefilm starring Alexa Vega, Lisa Vidal, Elizabeth Rice,
Alicia Morton, Leah Pipes, Shari Dyon Perry, Joey Nappo, and Chad Biagini.
First aired April 4, 2005 on Lifetime, the film is based on the book Odd Girl
Out: The Hidden Culture of Aggression in Girls by Rachel Simmons.
It sheds light onto the topic of school bullying among school girls.
The film explores themes of high school, bullying, bully, bullied, school bully.
The tone is dark and emotional.